Made in the USA
压制:随Feng
美国制造
Demi Lovato
歌手
Our love runs deep like a chevy
我们的爱如雪佛兰那般深厚
If you fall I'll fall with you baby
宝贝 如果你衰败 我会跟你一起衰落
Cause that's the way we like to do it
因为我们以这种方式去做事情
That's the way we like
这就是我们喜欢的方式
You run around open doors like a gentleman
您乐于助人敞开大门像一个绅士
Tell me girl every day you're my everything
她每天都告诉我这是我的一切
Cause that's the way you like to do it
因为我们以这种方式去做事情
That's the way you like
这是你喜欢的方式
Just a little West Coast, and a bit of sunshine
仅有的西海岸 仅有的一点阳光
Hair blowing in the wind, losing track of time
头发在风中飘逸 时间在缓缓流逝
Just you and I, just you and I
只有你和我 只有你和我在这里
Woah, woah
No matter how far we go, I want the whole world to know
不管我们走多远 我只想全世界知道
I want you bad, and I won't have it any other way
我想你坏 我不会有任何其他方式
No matter what the people say,
不管别人怎么说
I know that we'll never break
我知道 我们永远不会失败
Cause our love was made, made in the USA
因为我们的爱 在美国制造
Made in the USA, yeah
在美国制造 耶
You always reading my mind like a letter
你像个字母般一直在我脑海里萦绕
When I'm cold, you're there like a sweater
当我感冒时 你在我身边如毛衣般温暖
Cause that's the way we like to do it
因为我们以这种方式去做事情
That's the way we like
这就是我们喜欢的方式
And never ever let the world get the best of you
永远不会让世界得到最好的你
Every night we're apart, I'm still next to you
每晚我们分开时 我始终在你旁边
Cause that's the way I like to do it
因为我们以这种方式去做事情
That's the way I like
这是我喜欢的方式
We touch down on the east coast
我们降落在东海岸
Dinner in the sky rise,
晚宴在天空中兴起
winter is the best time for walking in the city lights
走在城市灯光下是冬天的最佳时光
You and I, you and I
你和我 我和你
Woah woah
No matter how far we go, I want the whole world to know
不管我们走多远 我想全世界都知道
I want you bad, and I wont have it any other way
我要你坏 我不会有任何其他方式
No matter what the people say,
不管人们说什么
I know that we'll never break
我知道 我们永远不会失败
Cause our love was made, made in the USA
因为我们的爱 在美国制造
Cause baby I'll bite the bullet
因为宝贝 我会硬着头皮
And take the blow for love
为了爱打破一切
Woahhhh, our love was made in the USA
Woahhhh我们的爱是美国制造
Made in the USA, made in the USA
美国制造  美国制造
No matter how far we go, I want the whole world to know
不管我们走多远 我想全世界都知道
I want you bad, and I wont have it any other way
我要你坏 我不会有任何其他方式
No matter what the people say,
不管人们说什么
I know that we'll never break
我知道 我们永远不会打破
Cause our love was made, made in the USA
因为我们的爱 在美国制造
Made in the USA, yeah
美国制造
Made in the U.S.
Made in the U.S.A
美国制造
压制:随Feng